<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CorkNFork</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_user">User</string>

    <string name="title_find">Find a:</string>
    <string name="title_meal">Meal</string>
    <string name="title_wine">Wine</string>

    <string name="username">Username</string>

    <string name="title_mealtypeselect">What are you eating?</string>
    <string name="title_winetypeselect">What are you drinking?</string>


    <string-array name="select_sort_items">
        <item>Highest rated</item>
        <item>Price low-high</item>
        <item>Price high-low</item>
        <item>Categorial</item>
        <item>Alphabetical</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="meal_activity_titles">
        <item>Eating Beef? Delicious!</item>
        <item>Eating pork? Good choice!</item>
        <item>Eating chicken? Not bad!</item>
        <item>Eating vegan?</item>
        <item>Eating fish? Yummy!</item>
        <item>Eating shellfish? Someone\'s rich!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="meal_activity_descriptions">
        <item>Dishes that focuses on beef will primarily use a red wine to complement the dish</item>
        <item>Dishes that focuses on pork will primarily use a red wine to complement the dish</item>
        <item>Dishes that focuses on chicken will primarily use a red wine to complement the dish</item>
        <item>Dishes that focuses on vegetables will primarily use water to complement the dish</item>
        <item>Dishes that focuses on fish will primarily use a white wine to complement the dish</item>
        <item>Dishes that focuses on shellfish will primarily use a white wine to complement the dish</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="drink_activity_titles">
        <item> Red wine? Classic! </item>
        <item> White wine? Wonderful!</item>
        <item> Sparkling? Fizzy is the way to go!</item>
        <item> Rosé? Fancy!</item>
        <item> Whiskey? Daring!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="drink_activity_descriptions">
        <item> Because of high amount of tannins in red wine, which causes bitterness and complements fatty foods, red wine tastes good with beef</item>
        <item> Because of a lower amount of tannins in white wine, white usually pairs well with chicken and fish</item>
        <item> Because of it\'s bubbles, sparkling is generally paired with shellfish and appetisers. </item>
        <item> It is hard to generalize with rosé, but most rosés pair well with strong food or vegetarian foods.</item>
        <item> Because of the alcohol burn from whiskey, you want fatty foods to mute the burn. So a good pairing for whiskey is beef, or even chocolate. </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
